Guide to the Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records, 1893-2008.
Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records
- Series IV. Cornell University Theatre and Cornell Dramatic Club
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Young America, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 75)
    - Younger Generation, Undated (Box 59, Folder 76)
    - Zealous Guardian, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 77)
    - Zoo, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 78)